JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 11
CHILI PEPPER, PART 1
MORIOH LANDMARK #4
MORIOH GRAND HOTEL
HOW TO GET THERE: FROM TERMINAL #1,
TAKE THE "MORIOH GRAND
SWIMMING AREA" BUS
TO "MORIOH GRAND HOTEL".
SURROUNDED BY EXTRAVAGANT VILLAS,
THE MORIOH GRAND HOTEL OOZES
ELEGANCE AND OLD-WORLD CHARM,
AND FOR YEARS HAS BEEN
THE BELOVED GO-TO SPOT
FOR TRAVELERS TO MORIOH.
BESIDES ITS ACCOMMODATIONS,
THE HOTEL IS KNOWN FOR SERVING
MORIOH BEEF TONGUE TO CROWDS
OF ADORING REGULARS
AND TRAVELERS ALIKE.
EPISODE 12
CHILI PEPPER, PART 2